<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on thecoswi.com </title>
    <link>http://thecoswi.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on thecoswi.com </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 15:15:34 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://thecoswi.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Website creation</title>
      <link>http://thecoswi.com/services/website-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecoswi.com/services/website-creation/</guid>
      <description>We are deploying websites with Hugo. It&amp;rsquo;s awesome. Templating themes make the process much easier. BuiltWithHugo, may be the current new and &amp;lsquo;hotness&amp;rsquo; but we think it definitely makes things much easier to roll out. New features are always being rolled out.
Is a hugo built site for you? These are just some of the things that make Hugo great. Hugo is fast really, really fast!
 Fast prototyping Just worry about editing the content Main page, blogs, ecommerce No major backends to worry about Fast compile and build times</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jerrett Levensalor</title>
      <link>http://thecoswi.com/team/jerrett-levensalor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecoswi.com/team/jerrett-levensalor/</guid>
      <description>Technical evangelist advisor. We are constantly pushing the envelope to make automation a way of life. The mantra deploy fast, fail fast only if needed, but always keep moving forward. We want to make the process of taking ideas and startups in a direction that makes something tangible that you can see and interact with quickly. Let&amp;rsquo;s face it, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to get distracted, without time management we can all lose our way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring and analytics</title>
      <link>http://thecoswi.com/services/monitoring-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecoswi.com/services/monitoring-analytics/</guid>
      <description>We are building and testing integration services that will allow us to offer monitoring solutions for your website, sales, general performance and health of your busines. We love the features of Elastic and will soon be offering those solutions to you. Check back soon for more information.
If you have suggestions on specific requirements drop us an eamil at general@thecoswi.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Virtual phone and IVR</title>
      <link>http://thecoswi.com/services/phone-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecoswi.com/services/phone-ivr/</guid>
      <description>We can offer to build a fully functioning virtual phone system that is pay as you go and only pay for what you use. We offer a cloud-based contact center service that can help you offer the best customer service while still keeping costs low.
- One person wanting a professional sounding presense - Small to medium size business looking to save costs - Multi-partnernsips and route calls on time of day - Different levels of service tier 1 calls, tier 2 calls</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a business in days</title>
      <link>http://thecoswi.com/services/business-sales/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecoswi.com/services/business-sales/</guid>
      <description>We are working on a solution that will be a complete solution that you can initiate with a few details like the domain or idea you have and we can provide a working example with your idea and be ready to fully launch a working idea. We realize things will invariably change and require updates, but our mission is to keep people on track.
- From idea to the needed branding items (superawesomename.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://thecoswi.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecoswi.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are available during normal business hours, but we can get tied up so worse case leave a voicemail through our IVR or send an email at general@thecoswi.com and we will try to respond at our earliest convenience.
   Day Opening Hours     Tuesday 8:30am - 5:00pm   Wednesday 8:30am - 5:00pm   Thursday 8:30am - 5:00pm   Friday 8:30am - 5:00pm   Saturday Closed   Sunday Closed    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domain email setup </title>
      <link>http://thecoswi.com/services/domain-email-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecoswi.com/services/domain-email-setup/</guid>
      <description>Getting an email from your business domain makes all the difference to sounding professional even if it&amp;rsquo;s only one person at the company. We can help setup emails and assist with domain updates to get things going for whats called MX records and make sure they get where they need to be. It can be a challenge get all the updates correct. We can help.
Single email on a domain You select your email provider you would like to use and we can help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://thecoswi.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecoswi.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Wow! Don&amp;rsquo;t you love technology, and hate it too.
This project started out as a way to see how long it really takes to get a full website up and &amp;ldquo;out the door&amp;rdquo;. I also wanted to see what kind of issues roadblocks there
were and if I could make the process faster from idea to reality. There are many hurdles, most stemming from too many options and how do you know which to choose.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>