<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on thecoswi.com </title>
    <link>http://thecoswi.com/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on thecoswi.com </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 15:15:34 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://thecoswi.com/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Website creation</title>
      <link>http://thecoswi.com/services/website-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecoswi.com/services/website-creation/</guid>
      <description>Lorem markdownum aequalis strigis. Saetigeri iubeas, vultu huic alvum nondum de obside ut laniavit arbor palmis, cum quin. Rupes vetat videndo, armigerae crimen habet Priamum nec.
Ne verba patulosque numen vix libet Agitabitur signa lympha; non lacunae, mox cum tumulis quoque triste dictis. Ignibus inpatiens explorat, te tegens ferro nocere haud, et Dulichium tui male! Quo sed fuit flexit et hic die solido, gloria?
 Cum det dixit Parcarum qui spemque est Exit ex huic Quod consiste agitataque claustraque vicina videt lacertis Loquor videt Ardua non igne caelesti coniugis cognovi diversorum Per nunc pariterque saeva vindicet  Locus evicit loquuntur Tyrrhena omnes, obstipui pugnabant temptavit Phoco vati dabant deus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring and analytics</title>
      <link>http://thecoswi.com/services/monitoring-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecoswi.com/services/monitoring-analytics/</guid>
      <description>We are building and testing integration services that will allow us to offer monitoring solutions for your website, sales, general performance and health of your busines. We love the features of Elastic and will soon be offering those solutions to you. Check back soon for more information.
If you have suggestions on specific requirements drop us an eamil at general@thecoswi.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Virtual phone and IVR</title>
      <link>http://thecoswi.com/services/phone-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecoswi.com/services/phone-ivr/</guid>
      <description>We can offer to build a fully functioning virtual phone system that is pay as you go and only pay for what you use. We offer a cloud-based contact center service that can help you offer the best customer service while still keeping costs low.
- One person wanting a professional sounding presense - Small to medium size business looking to save costs - Multi-partnernsips and route calls on time of day - Different levels of service tier 1 calls, tier 2 calls</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a business in days</title>
      <link>http://thecoswi.com/services/business-sales/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecoswi.com/services/business-sales/</guid>
      <description>We are working on a solution that will be a complete solution that you can initiate with a few details like the domain or idea you have and we can provide a working example with your idea and be ready to fully launch a working idea. We realize things will invariably change and require updates, but our mission is to keep people on track.
- From idea to the needed branding items (superawesomename.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domain email setup </title>
      <link>http://thecoswi.com/services/domain-email-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecoswi.com/services/domain-email-setup/</guid>
      <description>Getting an email from your business domain makes all the difference to sounding professional even if it&amp;rsquo;s only one person at the company. We can help setup emails and assist with domain updates to get things going for whats called MX records and make sure they get where they need to be. It can be a challenge get all the updates correct. We can help.
Single email on a domain You select your email provider you would like to use and we can help.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>